All
right, let's do it live on a draft day
Thursday edition of the program. Merely
bow the great Z.
Hello. Weapons. Woo.
Load them up. Got to have them. Weapons.
Weapons. Weapons. Weapons. Give me
weapons. Give me weapons or Buckeyes.
Weapons are Buckeyes. If it's not a
weapon, Buckeyes are fine. But weapons
that are Buckeyes. Oh, baby. Oh, baby.
That sounds like double good.
>> It's a win for everybody. Uh, we've been
talking about this for a long time.
>> Look at that. I think that's the hotel
we stayed at in uh Pittsburgh.
>> It probably is, right?
>> Only two of them of consequence.
>> Yeah, I I recognize those. Uh,
>> where So, where this is set up um right
outside of Hinesfield. Is that where it
is? or what is it called now?
>> Acureer. Is it set up? Is that where
they're set up is right there?
>> Yeah.
>> Yes.
>> That would I think be tough from a
in-n-out perspective, would it not?
>> I believe that it would be.
>> I mean, you can't
>> Oh, it's a pain. Like, you're better off
parking on the other side and walking
over the bridge.
>> Over the bridge.
>> No offense, but they're running ESPN's
thing and they're having this welcome to
the draft and it's narrated by a Steeler
and they chose Ryan Clark, I guess, cuz
he's on the payroll. But I mean,
shouldn't this be like
>> Troy Palamalu or Hines Ward?
>> Hines Ward or Troy Yeah. would be my
pick on that. Speaking of Troy Palamalo,
there are people who suggest that Caleb
DS is 90% of Troy Palamalo.
>> Why are they limiting him?
>> Because he doesn't have the hair is the
10% that's missing the hair.
>> Also, they can take those Permany
sandwiches and just keep them over
there.
>> They can stick it, brother.
>> Those things suck. Yeah,
>> that's what I'll tell you about.
>> You know what? And they don't know how
to make a nacho. Contrary to what you've
heard, that nacho's garbage. Go. You
want a nacho? You want the nacho?
>> You want a press box nacho? Go to
Houston.
>> That's where you get your nachos.
>> Oh, baby.
>> Get you some protein in those nachos.
>> They got a giant block of, you know,
that good stuff. Case
>> and they're like shaving it in a heater
as it heats and it bubbles and they're
like, "Oh, you like some chorito?"
"Yeah, I would." Would you like that?
Oh, yeah. Then we're gonna now we're
gonna slowly mix in a little pico de
gallo in there and get it marinate. Oh,
goodness gracious.
>> Give me uh your dream nacho order right
now. What what is on the toppings there?
>> I know you like the guac more, but
>> it's got to be a It's got to be a white
cheese, a chihuahua or a a queso fresco.
It's got to be a white cheese. Um and
then I like definitely
jalapenos. They can be fresh. They can
be pickled in a nacho case. I'm not
going to discriminate. I prefer
>> fresh.
>> Sure.
>> We're going to have some uh tomatoes in
there. Some fresh tomatoes. I like them.
A little onion mixed in there. And then
I'm probably going to go my favorite
would be
probably a combo of and I don't know if
I've even seen this so can't it's my
favorite that I'm thinking of.
>> You're these are the flavors you want.
>> Yeah. Some chorito and some pulled pork
in there or like an al pastor nacho. I
>> Well, now you're really talking but then
I'm jalapeno out,
>> a little pineapple in, and a little
habanero fresh.
>> Now you're in.
>> In. Yeah.
>> Now you're in. I like what you did
there.
>> Thank you.
>> Uh what what do we make? We're We're
here. We've we've done it finally.
navigated it.
>> Let's go. What's that Adam Sandler movie
right now? 6 and 24.
>> What's that? The Great Sand do where
he's got the remote control and he can
speed it up.
>> I'm speeding up to
>> Let's get there.
>> We're on the clock. Yeah, that one.
Yeah. Very sad story. You don't want to
fast forward your life. Turns out
>> I No, I wouldn't want to.
>> No, me either. I love it.
>> Quick, even quicker than I am. Yeah. Um,
but yeah, this is where we're at. So,
you're it's it's today is the draft. You
got two picks at six and 24. There are
myriad rumors out there about multiple
teams trying to trade back starting with
Arizona in a big way at number three.
The question would be what type of
player would elicit a trade up? Uh I
think we have I think correctly surmised
a defensive end for example Arville Ree
slipping to three or potentially
slipping beyond that. And then
>> the other thing that's going to be a big
topic tonight is going to be Jeremiah
Love. And as we get closer and closer,
it's funny it kind of starts where it
begins in a certain extent. Uh Mendoza
has always been number one overall. Love
has always been kind of the catalyst
here. And it's just a matter of do it a
draft where
the the money positions, the the big
money positions, quarterback, receiver,
and I don't know why there's there's
much doubt on these receivers. I think
this is a really good group of
receivers. And I I think obviously
Tate's my favorite. Tyson I've seen I
haven't seen as much of and obviously
the injury stuff is there. Uh with
Carnell Tate, you throw him the ball, he
catches it. It's pretty simple. He's got
good size. He gets good separation.
Never see him caught from behind. Good
contested catch guy. Um I'd be
hardressed to imagine him not being some
variation of T. Higgins in the NFL. And
I think most teams would sign up for
that who need receivers.
>> So inject it into my veins.
>> Yeah. Uh Jordan Tyson, I'm not going to
sit here and tell you. I know feels like
he's a little more twitchy and and that
type of stuff. There's injury stuff
there with him that there isn't with
Tate. So I think maybe that's part of
>> they're both going to go in the top 10.
It feels like it.
>> It does feel like it. It does. Um, if I
were to say to you, the draft starts
where? What's your answer to that?
>> Probably two, but I feel pretty good.
>> There's a party going on there.
>> It's a luminary. Mr. Cook's here because
he's going to join us momentarily.
>> That I feel like it's at two, but I
think we know that's going to be an it's
going to be Reese or Bailey.
>> Yeah.
>> So then I think where it gets wide open
where you don't know the position or
anything is three. Yeah. Arizona.
>> Now, Jerry Jones has said that, you
know,
>> they can't trade into the top five, and
he said that specifically. Well, you
happen to be number six.
>> Yeah.
>> So, that's interesting to me. Um,
I've seen trades that involve us with
the Rams. I've seen a trade down from
Ben Albbright that has us trading to 20
from six to 23 with the Eagles.
>> That has to include a 271
>> or else it's a non-starter for me. Yeah.
Um, and that might be a non-sar for me
anyway. That's a that's seems a pretty
robust place to go.
>> The Eagles and the Rams are the two 20
two teams who could think about trading
a 271 and not worry too much about it
just because they feel like they're
going to pick in the box third of that
draft. Um, nobody who has a chance,
nobody who's an injury away from picking
in the top five is trading a 271.
>> Right. If you could somehow end up at 13
and get a 271, I'd be okay with that
tradeback. And then my my target would
be cuz I think Tyson Table would be gone
would be Mai Lemon.
>> That would be my target. And now you got
your slot, you got your Aman Ross Brown,
quarterback favorite guy. You know, Jerk
Goff certainly loves having Aman Ross
Brown there. You'd have him and Fannon
in the middle of the field. Judy and
Bond out wide.
>> Okay. All right. I could I could start
to get excited about that. So, we'll
see. Um
yeah,
I just keep going back for me to what
Joe Thomas said that you got to build
the band before you worry about
the the bodyguards.
>> It was such an incredible um and and he
flat out said that directly to us. He
said it multiple times and and you would
think he would know because he is on the
alltime NFL team. If you're playing at
left tackle, he's one of two or three
guys. He's one of them. Um and
>> run that by Glenn. We say, "We heard
this.
>> We heard this from the
>> philosophy. What do you think?
>> What do you think about it?"
>> Yeah.
>> Um but his that that that was such a
great analogy of you can be the best
balancer in the world, but if you're not
protecting a great band, what are you
doing?
>> All right. The band, brother. Yeah. So,
that's that's the thing that that
hopefully we're at. And we've done the
we talked about this a billion. We did
ad this is the exact same thing we were
saying last year
>> at this time was was weapons weapons
weapons and we this year we did the
data. We did it last year too in terms
of playoff teams and the points scored
that is required to be a team that's a
playoff team. Like you got to score
points in this league one way or
another. And and so um that's something
that's going to have to be addressed.
And then the other part for our organ
organization is um you we need we need
some foundational pieces. If you're
picking at six that that should be a
multiple Pro Bowl guy. That should be
someone who gets a couple of contracts
here. That's that's someone who should
be a Brown for the next decade when
you're picking that high in the draft.
So um that's part of it too.
>> It's got to be somebody who raises your
floor and your ceiling.
>> Yeah. Well put.
>> That's just that's what it's got to this
has to be a foundational piece. I mean,
you this is the draft class that will be
on its rookie contract, initial rookie
contract. This is the draft class that
will be in the new building.
>> Yeah. Yep. Yep. And you'd love nothing
more than to open that building and have
their picture on the side of it and say,
"Here's the contract extension we've
done for fill in the blank and we're
happy that they're going to spend the
rest absolutely spend the rest of their
their their career here and they're
going to be a Brown for life." I mean,
that's that's the objective when you
pick this high. You have to hit in that
type of way.
I'm known to lead a witness. So when we
had Glender, can we do you is this too
leading of a question?
>> Go ahead.
>> Who are we picking at six and why is it
Carnell tape?
>> I don't I think I I support it. I
support your line of question. I support
your verbiage.
>> Um and and I'm down I I am down with it.
Absolutely. Uh we will get to Mr. Cook
coming up next. Those are your hot
topics today presented by University
Hospitals, official healthcare partner
of your Cleveland Browns. Celebrate the
excitement of the NFL draft at the crib
presented by Howard Hannah. Join Browns
alumni Josh Cribs, Aaron Shay, and
Chomps today 3 to 54339
Oakidge Trail in Brunswick 44212. Agent
Gary Benzina as they educate you on the
market and help you draft your dream
home. More details at
howardhana.com/gobs.
>> Let's go, baby. Yeah,
>> we got Cribs all three days. We got
Cribs all three days.
>> Cribs is coming up uh I think at 3:30.
>> How about it? on the program. We got uh
Ben Albbright on the program today.
Little insider. See what see how he
describes this Eagles trade that he has
in his mock draft. And we got a little
bit of a mailbag.
>> Yeah. Good. I'm glad we talked to Ben.
Nice.
>> Yeah. So, there you go. That's what you
have to look forward to, which is nice.
On a draft day Thursday, you're
listening to Cleveland Browns Daily.
We're presented by Valley Bet, official
sports betting partner Cleveland Browns.
Please bet responsibly and presented by
Howard Hannah, official real estate
partner of your Cleveland Browns.
All
right, we're back. Cleveland Browns
daily add more fun to your fandom with
the Valley Bet Sports Book app. Download
today, get 50 back in bonus bets, you
place your first wager of 10 or more.
Ballet Bet, official sports betting
partner of your Cleveland Browns. joined
in studio by a great friend of the
program, your assistant general manager,
vice president of player personnel,
Glenn Cook, in studio.
>> At this point, we're 4 hours plus
>> from the draft. How much of the hay is
in the barn?
>> Hopefully all the I mean, the only hay
left is is now the uh the chaos of
trades or you know, movement. So um you
know right now all the teams myself
included are
checking the right phone phone number
you know of of the counterpart at the uh
other organization to make sure you have
a the right number but yeah I'd say most
of it's in the barn. We feel pretty good
about where we are
>> in this process and finally have you
know six and 24 having the two ones
three of the top 39. How does that kind
of change going through the simulations
that you guys go through? How does that
change kind of your whole approach as
opposed to a couple times we've had to
wait until the third round to make a
pick?
>> I mean, the approach is to take the best
guy you can find, right? The best player
available to you at the time that fits
what you need, etc., etc. So, um, how it
changes is we have more options. Um, we
have more opportunities to add players
to the team. Uh, I think our scenario
stuff a couple days ago was pretty fun
because, um, there's a there's a couple
ways this thing can play out, especially
with how it's shaping up this year. So,
um, in terms of our process process, it
doesn't change much, but it does open up
a lot more options when you have two
picks in the top 25.
>> In those scenarios, who makes the pick
for the Cleveland Browns? Do you guys
rotate?
>> Uh, our group does, you know, so like,
uh, well, so there's there's us in the
room. We'll have discussion on it. I
would say there's not one person making
the pick. Um, we'll have discussion on
what you would do in the scenario, but
we actually let the group make the pick.
And it's it's it's a it's a good
exercise to kind of see how your
department, a little bit of the coaching
staff maybe feels about, hey, if this is
where we're sitting, who we would take
um in in the exercise, but as it relates
to people who are in the room, we just
kind of talk through it. Yeah. There's
not like a hey, a final pick.
>> We'd be fun scenario, guys.
>> Yeah, I'd love to scenario. We
scenarios. I think they probably have an
idea of our scenarios.
>> They probably do. I guess
>> I know. I definitely know yours.
>> Um you've been at this a while. you've
been in these rooms a while. How
how has your approach to it changed with
experience? Um my hunch is that and
correct me if I'm wrong, but when you're
young in this game, like do you get
connected to certain prospects and then
do you try to separate that part as
you've gone along with it?
>> Yeah, I think the truth of it is when
you're young, you think you know, right?
You think you have all the answers. Um
not all the answers, but you feel pretty
confident about your position on
something, right? And at times you
cannot be moved by new information. So
you know the the all-star games happen
and the com mine happens and then you
get medical information and then you get
to spend time with them on 30 visits or
at their at their proday. Um they test
uh you get more medical information,
right? So all these different, you know,
pieces of things about their background
get brought together and and I I can
only speak for myself when I was
younger. was like, "Yeah, but I think he
can do this or I don't think he's good."
You know, so like you're very stubborn.
I think as as I've gained more
experience and and hopefully wisdom,
it's being able to update, you know,
appropriately across all those different
checkpoints because you don't want to
sway too far one way or the other and
use your wisdom and your experience, but
just being able to update as more
information comes in and and not anchor
yourself to it's got to be this guy or
it's got to be this position
>> and and realizing that, hey, you know,
you may take a player who you you're not
as maybe elated about and he comes in
and and he makes your team much better
and it's just a it's a it's a you know
quiver in your hat for the future to say
hey it's not always about how you feel
but about doing doing what's best for
the org um
>> across all those decisions and I think
that's the part where at least
personally I've grown where it's like
hey this is what's best for our team um
trying to take myself out of it as much
as possible and I think the group pushes
each other to make sure we all do that
like hey is this are we actually doing
what's right for us and not I want to
take this guy because every year we you
know we all talk like we all love ball
so we all talk and
>> you know it's like I know this guy's
going to be a good he's gonna come in
and play well in the league and you can
ignore some other things and you step
back and you know 17 weeks into the
season you're like man this dude's
balling or it's like hey he maybe he's
struggling a little bit more than I
thought he would and uh two years in
three years in and now that I've been
for 15 having seen
>> I was talking to someone you know like I
after you see your first draft get to
their free agency you're like man,
there's a lot of lessons
in in what's happening uh four years
later. So, all those things I try to
apply and get better at each year and I
think we do too.
>> Yeah.
>> This is something that just popped into
my mind as you were talking about things
that you've learned.
>> Is there like a position that you've
found that you have had a better success
rate with or a position that maybe you
struggle with? You don't have to name
what they are, but just like as you go
through it, because part of me was
thinking like, you know, the way that
scouting and maybe I'm totally wrong,
but guys have areas, right? They have
regions.
>> I wonder if someday with all the
information we're able to get through
and I don't know if you if it's even a
trackable thing like, oh, this guy
happens to be really good with
receivers. This guy happens to be really
good with safeties. So, maybe have like
a position scout, you know, these are
the receivers we like. Let's send our
receiver guy to go get in the mix. It's
definitely something you should be able
to track after enough time, you know,
like maybe not after.
>> Is there a position you feel the most
comfortable watching? I mean, I mean,
the one I feel most is L. Yeah, you
know, it's like one of those where I you
understand intimately what they're being
asked to do most of the time at the
position
>> and what it should look like, right?
You've I've felt it. Yeah.
>> So, I know when you jolt a lineman, you
know, what it looks like at an elite
level, what it looks like at at an okay
level, and then where you're like, "Hey,
this guy actually struggles in service."
So, that was going to be my easy answer.
Like linebacker is just one of those
things where I don't I don't take it for
granted. I still
>> It's in your DNA.
>> Yeah. I still trust the process on it.
Um, in terms of watching film and and
all that, but like that's one of those
where
>> when I'm passionate about it, you know,
I can probably be a little stubborn at
backer. The rest of it,
>> there's some I've gotten a lot better
at. there somewhere still like and and
and you have to be honest with yourself
where it's like hey
I like this guy but I know sometimes I
can I can run hot on I'm using this
example on tight ends right or it's like
hey this type of corner may not be my
style but like step back and
>> he's good
>> just evaluate the player right so I
think there's one some self-awareness
and then I think as a leader which this
is on Andrew and on myself um and I've
seen it at other places the GM also has
to know his people right and you kind of
know okay when six people or speaking in
the room, you know, this one scout when
he steps in on a receiver like he knows,
you know, like or you know, this one
particular scout when he talks about a
lineman, like
>> I'm going to put a little bit more
weight on it. And that's that's the
balancing act of
>> of the role as well when you're
listening to your people because not
everyone gets the same weight on
everything, you know, that's just the
reality of life. So, I think um there's
definitely some but there's definitely
some positions where people just
naturally are better. We've heard a lot
kind of in the media, not in and I don't
know if teams talk about this. If you
call up and say, "Hey, how many how many
first round grades do you guys have this
year, there's a perception in the media
again, that this is a draft that where
there are not 32 first round grades in
this draft class. How do you guys go
about doing that?" And I think people
sometimes they get a shock when they
figure out how many people are actually
on your board when you if you just
multiply the number of picks in draft,
it's a much smaller subset than that
that would be even on our board to be
drafted.
32 guys have to get drafted. That's
what, you know, that's what Andrew
always says. Like, you can talk about
how many should, but there's 32 picks,
right?
>> And at some point, you're going to have
to make picks. So, our job is just to
put them in the right spot and put the
right value and feel comfortable with
how they're going to fit into our team
and our organization. And then you you
have to draft players, right? Like even,
you know, we're very much a team that
wants picks and wants the assets and
etc. to make good decisions and make
more decisions, but you're doing all
that to get players. So, how do we put
oursel in the best position within each
round to get the guys that we think can
help us win?
>> Is that something that's weighed in?
Like, we're picking at six, right? I
think everybody would agree there are at
least six first rounders in this draft,
right? Maybe not six blue chip guys, but
six first rounders in this draft.
>> How do you guys weigh in a tradeback
scenario
where you see the number of guys that
you really want? like does that really
factor into those discussions? Like
we're not moving out of our comfort.
>> Yeah. Not not to get way deep deep into
it. Not that it's like that complicated,
but it's not only hey, there's six guys
we think deserve to be in the first
round, but it's also
>> you're you're assessing how other teams
may, you know, so you're trying to
predict, hey, this is these are their
needs, you know, these are the positions
that they would target. Honestly, this
is their historical philosophy on
drafting in this slot. first round,
second round, fifth round, right? So,
all those things factor into in terms
of, hey, you know, we feel pretty good,
>> pretty positioned to do what we need to
do here or it's like, hey, you know, we
should think about, you know, moving on
the board somewhere to to better give
ourselves a chance to get the guy that
that you want to target here, you know.
So, um it's not just,
>> hey, there's 40 guys we were taking the
second round. It's also you have to
account for
>> it's an auction everybody else seems
doing the same thing, you know. So,
>> this is a uh it's a simple question,
probably a complicated answer. Why is
this so hard? And and I'll give you an
example. The San Francisco 49ers went
all in on Tre Lance. Give up all these
assets. They go all the way up to get
him.
>> They end up with their franchise
quarterback with the last pick in the
whole draft. From a fan looks at this
and goes, "How does that happen? How how
do we how are you so convinced?" And I'm
not picking on them. Obviously, they
have won a ton and they they're one of
the model organizations, but it's just
an example of they were all in on this
one guy
>> and then there's a throwin guy at the
end truly Mr. Irrelevant who ends up
being their franchise quarterback in a
$400 million deal.
>> Why is it so hard?
>> I don't know.
>> No, no. I mean, it really is though. I
mean, it's such a fascinating thing to
me.
>> It really is, right? Because you you
would think um and I talk about this all
the time. um you know multi-billion
dollar organizations have all the
resources at our disposable disposal uh
some really smart people in these
positions. I think
look in order for you to be a GM like
you for the most part I've had to earn
that role. So you know there's a lot of
respect to the role and a lot of
experience and time putting put into
developing these different skills needed
to make these decisions.
>> And even with all that it's just really
hard. It's really hard to understand how
a human is going to develop, you know,
or integrate themselves into an
organization,
>> how they're going to fit into your
organization and and then how they're
going to fit into your city. Uh how the
things that come with just also being a
human with life that will come with you
being drafted in the NFL, depending on
where you're taken, depending on the
city that you're moving to, depending on
your family dynamic. Um, we do our best
to try to anticipate all those different
things and put the resources in play in
place for them to be successful. It just
doesn't always work out, you know, and
that's before you get to anything on
field, you know, does he stay healthy?
>> Um, does he remain confident when when
he when he, you know, starts to have
some
>> some uh adversity? Uh, you know, how
does he overcome it? Do is he in a room
that actually fits his personality and
that can help support his development?
You know, it's just there's just so many
different variables that
>> for as smart as a lot of people who do
this are like we can't anticipate it
all. We can't perfectly uh figure it
out. And so you will have you will have
misses. That's why you do other things
that compensate or still allow you um on
the whole to still be a good team and
still be a good org, right? Like that's
why people have different, you know,
drafting philosophies or pick
philosophies or team building
philosophies that cover up for just the
error that comes from being people.
>> Yeah. Like that's just imperfect.
>> It's clearly difficult to truly
understand somebody's competitive nature
and who are the people that really just
need to get the most out of their
talents. I think that's clearly a hard
thing to accurately ascertain. I think
people know what to say
>> and you just don't always know what it's
actually going to be. And when the
competition goes up, that's when it gets
exposed, right? It's easy when you're at
a big school and you're playing people
that just shouldn't really necessarily,
they deserve to be on the field with
you, but they're not going to be playing
on Sundays. I think that's the And then
the other thing is, I don't know about
you guys, I'll speak for myself, the
most unpredictable me that I could ever
have been if is if I was a 20-year-old
millionaire who was idolized by a lot of
people. I would have been I have no idea
what I would have been. And I think
that's an honor.
>> That's a variable that we now we know.
is helping with that.
>> Now, you know, you're getting you're
getting more
>> you're getting more data about how they
going to behave if when they got a lot
of stuff cuz these guys, some of these
cats are going to be taking a pay cut.
>> I definitely
>> second round picks.
>> I would have been spending a lot of
money.
>> No doubt. All right. One draft kind of
philosophy question. This is something
he and I have talked about and it came
from Joe Thomas actually. And so there's
a lot of talk of, you know, do you build
inside out? So on the line, this is on
offensive side of the ball. Do you build
that line and it helps you score? You're
already smiling. or do you accumulate
the weapons and the quarterback and all
of that? And so we had a conversation
with Joe Thomas and he put it in a way
that I'd never heard before that
resonated with with us and I'm just
curious to hear what you think about it.
So what Joe said is the offensive line
is the reality is like they're the
bodyguards for a band.
>> Okay.
>> And when he says when you have the best
band in the world when you're the number
one band in the world, you need the best
bodyguards. There's just more people
trying to get near these people. You
need more bodyguards to help that band
function at the level it needs to to be
the number one band in the world. when
you're a garage band, you don't
necessarily need the best bodyguards.
You can you can work that up. And so his
idea was I want to build the band and
this is coming from obviously I think
the greatest left tackle to play games
like I want to build the band and the
weapons that we need to protect before
necessarily building the bodyguards out.
So that never I never heard it that way
and I thought it was interesting coming
from him as an offensive line. I think
you'd be like offensive line all day
long. So how do you balance that? I know
that it's not it is a gray issue. It is
not a black and white issue but how do
you kind of balance that and from a
philosophical standpoint? I'm not going
to give I may not give the answer but my
my analogy is your O line is the
foundation of a house you know so okay
>> um I think we all know how important it
is to make sure once you lay that
foundation right when you do all the
digging and all the things that you have
to do underground that you build a
really really good foundation and to me
the skill players are your finishing you
know your finishing touches like all the
trinkets now those are important too
because as we know our wives
>> thanks to this hailtorm I'm getting all
new receivers our wives Our wives love
finishes, right? Like and it puts a lot
of value on the house and you know it
helps you sell it. So I I think
>> like we we are not building a uh
expansion team. Andrew uses the
expansion analogy, but we're not
building expansion team. So like um part
of I think how you approach that team to
team is where you are individually as a
team, right? So, I mean, if a new GM
comes in and he feels like his O line is
is is in a position where um it's good
enough for them to go out and play, then
yeah, he should probably be pretty
aggressive and and go get some
playmakers to help his quarterback and
help the team. Um,
>> you know, if you feel it's it's vice
versa where we have targets and weapons,
but it may be tough for us to protect
and run the football and and, you know,
play four-minute football when we need
to, then I, you know, I would assume you
you might think it's more important to
address your own line. So, I think um
and all the theories are great, but I
think at the same time, you're building
a team, so you got to understand where
your team is at and uh what you need in
that moment.
>> Uh there's I would say there's not just
like a onesize fit all like philosophy.
>> Well, we'll find out. We got two picks
in the first round and we might need
both.
>> We'll know. Yeah. So, we'll see which
one's prioritized tonight. That'll be
fun. Anybody the best. Thank you as
always on draft day. Great to have you
here. General manager, vice president,
player personnel, Glenn Cook in studio.
You listen to Cleveland Browns daily on
8:50 ESPN.
Add more fun to your fandom. The Ballet
Bet Sports Book app. Download today. Get
50 back in bonus bets. You place your
first wager of 10 or more. Ballet Bet
official sports bidding partner of your
Cleveland Browns. We head out on the
hotline. Browns legend Josh Cribs joins
from the crib.
>> I ain't got it.
>> You there, buddy?
>> Yo,
>> we got you,
>> sir. Draft week open houses. Howard
Hannah, you're there. The Cribs, where
are you at, man?
>> Man, we're in Brunswick. The crib.
Howard Hannah is in Brunswick and it's
in full swing. People coming and going.
I just did an interview and people are
looking at the house already. So, it's
in full effect out here in Brunswick.
>> 4339 Oakidge Trail in Brunswick, in
fact, is where Mr. Cribs will be. I
believe Chomps is out there, too. you
have that to look forward to which is
very very nice. It's draft day buddy. Uh
what is what does this day mean to you?
Um just in terms of from a fan
perspective as a guy who went undrafted
and then had the incredible career that
you did. What is what does today kind of
mean for you?
>> Well, you know, speaking from, you know,
a guy who was in the NFL and knew that
it was a draft day. You know, it's a lot
of lives that going to change on this
day. Not just people that's drafted, but
their families. You know, also guys that
are currently in the NFL, they have to
have the testament to understand that
look, there's always going to be players
younger, faster that they can pay less
to come and almost do the job that you
do. So, you have to play even more than
you're doing the year before. So, you
know, it's a, like I said, it's a lot of
lives that's going to change. I was a
free agent, so I knew that I had draft
picks in front of me. You got to play
the best. You got to be the best at this
level. And I'm excited for those young
guys coming in to change this football
team for the best.
>> What do you want to see happen tonight?
Browns have picked six and 24. What how
do you want to see that? And of course,
we're talking with the threetime pro
bowler, twotime AllPro, Josh Cribs from
the Cribs.
>> Yes. Look here, and I've been talking
about it all day. This is what makes
sense to me. And and and I was, you
know, talking to a lot of the guys here
and and and Aaron Shay is here with me.
We was going over as well. At number
six, I believe that if we don't trade,
you just do the no-brainer. Go ahead and
take, you know, Carnell Tate, satisfy
that wide receiver need.
>> We agree. We agree. Let's go.
>> Is not there.
>> Yes. If Carnell Tate is not there, and
if there's another, you know, surprising
pick that I won't be mad at if if
Jeremiah Love is there. I know we got
Juckens. He's firing off on all
cylinders. But if we have a chance to
have a a Nick Chub, Kareem Hunt
reincarnation, why not? Why not give
those guys something special and then
still have some juice to go go and get a
receiver at 24 or offensive lineman? I
think this is a a draft where you're
loaded with receivers who might be taken
after the the top 10. So, saying all of
that, I think that valuable uh wide
receiver picks will be available if they
trade out of the six the six uh picks,
>> but not out of the first round. And I'm
talking about going back to, you know,
10, 11, 12, something like that, and
still get a valued receiver and still
had that 24th pick to get a value at
offensive line.
>> Yeah, it's and Josh, it's it's weapons,
right? You gotta be feared.
>> Weapons.
>> Teams got to fear you a little bit.
>> I'll be mad. Exa, guys. I'll be mad if
we go defense. I I know Caleb DS is, you
know, a really good talent and a lot of
people say, "Hey, take the best person
there." We we got the best people on
defense. We got a we got a Miles Garrett
and I got to speak of him like he's a
Hulk. Like we got a Hulk, right? And and
we still fell short, you know, of
playoffs. But we need the offensive uh
counterpart to help score points cuz
guess what the Hulk in Miles Garrett, he
was scoring points, too, jumping over,
blocking field goals, but we need an
offensive counterpart to match that. And
wide receiver, depending on who our QB
is, he needs a big time wide receiver to
go with him.
>> Couldn't agree more. I think it's about
weapons. You're trying to keep up with
the Bengals in this division. you're
trying to keep up with the Ravens and a
potent offense with a two-time MVP and
and a Steelers team that might have
Aaron Rogers back and has DK Mechaf and
Michael Pitman at wide receiver.
>> So, you got to score.
>> You got to be able to score the
football.
>> You know, in talking to talking to
people like you, uh, Nathan, you you
just opened up my mind a little bit. So,
you see all this keeping up with the
weapons that they have to we have to do.
Yep.
>> That's why it makes sense to me almost
to trade back just a little to open up
cuz that six is so valuable so valuable
that we could possibly, you know, get,
you know, more than what's needed. We
possibly get two receivers and get, you
know, two linemen and a receiver with
trading down just a little bit with that
number 24. We probably get a couple more
picks out of that and for next year. So
value is what Andrew Barry loves to do.
So he might it might make sense to trade
out of that for value and still get the
talent that we need.
>> Josh, you mentioned I'm gonna give you a
scenario. You mentioned Jeremiah Love.
He's there at six. You get a call from
the Rams and they say 13 this year,
which is their the pick that they have,
and a number one next year to move up to
six. Do you do it?
>> Oh. Oh, I that's going to be a real
that's going to be a serious discussion.
I I may have to do that to get another
number one for next year. You may have
to pull that trigger because your
receivers will still be there. Your
offensive line will still be there and
you'll still have the 24th pick.
>> You still got 24.
>> Makes so much sense. You still get 24.
You still get 13, which means you still
will have one of those elite premier
receivers on the board cuz all of them
can't go in top 10. So, one of those
guys will still be available for you.
And those offensive linemen, I know they
say it's going to be a run on offensive
lineman, but guess what? is more of them
available at 24. So with that scenario,
I would definitely take it.
>> I would sprint to take that.
>> Now if that pick from the Rams is going
to be probably bottom four or five picks
of next year's draft,
>> it's just ammunition to move up. And it
also takes a player that if you really
liked, you're I'm guessing if you're
moving back to 13, you're saying I'm
still getting somebody I really like.
And now you're getting that guy. You're
getting two players. And this is a team
that's got a lot of needs, quite
frankly. So you're getting two first
round talents for one. That's typically,
you know, they're theoretical.
>> Might not like it, though.
>> I think if you got a 271, I think I
think if you get a 271, fans will be
thrilled with that because everybody's
talking
>> anytime you get a pick for the next
year.
>> Yes, you're absolutely correct. And
you'll have to educate fandom. You have
to educate them on that. But they will
look at that and say, you know what,
Miles Garrett wants to win right now.
You know what? Our fan base wants to win
right now. We're not walk worrying about
next year. We want to we talking about
this year. So that would I can foresee
would be the only issue. Cooler heads
will prevail. I'll take that deal.
Again, like I said, I'll pull my back
out uh blow blow a hamstring to make
that move. I'm with you on that one.
>> Right. And I It's You say, "Listen, we
only had one pick in the top 13 this
year. We still have one pick in the top
13 this year. Now we also have a pick
next year." And when we made the trade
from two to five, we picked up, you
know, the pick that became Quinn Sean
Judkins, as well as the one this year,
which is pick number 24. And we got so
we got Mason Graham, Quinshan Judkins,
and this pick all for, you know, what's
turned out to be Travis Hunter, who is
now going to be a full-time corner,
which is also kind of wild that how that
things have changing one year, one year
down there. What's kind of is that
that's the energy you're getting from
the from the Browns fans? They want
weapons and and don't want to trade.
>> I know.
>> Weapons. Yeah, weapons.
>> Weapons. Weapons. weapons cuz if you
look at last year we we if you look at
our last year situation right we shored
up we did a good job showing up when we
picked Mason Graham and we had and
everyone kind of looked around even you
know you look at that first top five
pick you look at you know you want
excitement you want weapons but we
couldn't argue with something that gave
us a shorthanded thing in Mason Grant
even if it didn't show up in the score
or win column that was something that
hey we desperately needed to to had uh
you know give Miles Garrett a
counterpart, but when we look at this
year, I will be upset if we're looking
at a Caleb DS or you know a defensive
guy who will all will add something to
an already good defense. I would be
upset with with especially with the
needs on offense and I and I think uh
Andrew would do a good job at satisfying
the needs. He did it in free agency sat
very satisfactory in free agency. um
known to struggle, not him personally,
but known to struggle picking wide
receivers. A lot of sometimes he gets a
bad rep for that. And I think this will
be the draft to rectify that and get a
guy who can come in right away and and
and make a difference.
>> The Crib is a three-day openhouse series
held during NFL draft week, combining
the energy of football, the spring home
buying season across Cleveland
communities. Events will take place
across northeast Ohio in Brunswick,
Morland Hills, and Avon. Each featuring
Browns alumni and fan focused elements
inside active home listings. The one
that Josh is at today, 4339 Oakidge
Trail in Brunswick is the address on
that one. Um, all right, buddy. Dream
scenario, let's just say we stay at 6
and 24. Um, you mentioned Tate receiver,
something like that at six. Is that the
your preference to goate Carell Tate at
six and then at 24 you want Absolutely.
You want to go offensive tackle at 24 or
what do you want to go
>> offensive offensive tackle or allaround
guy? A lot of them will be off the board
by that time. So we'll probably get a
guy that's you know can double as a
center offense, you know, adding more uh
uh consistency and depth to the
offensive line.
>> That's music to our ears, buddy.
>> Let's go. Yes. That's it. That's it.
That's what a lot of people want. Yep.
>> Yep. That's it. All right, pal.
>> I don't think anybody would be mad at
that. That's I think we can all toast to
that. Yeah. Yeah.
>> I think you're right. Appreciate you,
buddy. Have time out at the cribs out
there, pal.
>> Absolutely, guys. Thank you so much. It
was fun, man. See you guys later.
>> Josh Cribs, Browns alumni. Uh Chomps is
out there. He said Aaron Sheay is out
there as well. Uh the Cribs, as I
mentioned, a three-day openhouse series.
NFL draft week tonight. Today in
Brunswick, that's from 3:00 to 5:00.
Then Morland Hills, I believe, tomorrow.
and then Avon on Saturday featuring
Browns alumni fan focused elements uh
and all sorts of things. So there you go
in uh all part of Howard Hannah and the
Crib Draft Week open houses. We had
Glenn Cook in here before Josh joined
us. Um
>> that it's tough. I I would imagine as we
were talking to him, I imagine that's
tough for him too because he he doesn't
really want to say anything. No,
>> we're not going to put him in a bad spot
to say anything. Um but it is the the
key to this thing, you know, tonight is
going to be um
no matter how you no matter how this
this dinner is put together, no matter
what the ingredients are, if you are
getting two players or potentially three
players out of this first round, what
really what folks are going to remember
in the long run is that is how good
those players are. So it doesn't really
matter the order of it. We're worried
about the order of it right now. we want
Carnell and then go tackle at 24 or
whatever. But if if the tackle at is at
six and the receivers's at 24 and
they're both dudes, nobody cares. If you
trade out a six and you pick at at 12,
20 and 24, as long as they're all dudes,
it doesn't matter. But they need to be
dudes because that's that's the only way
you got to score and then you got to
draft your own guys and get those guys
to second contracts and thirds. That's
how you have sustained success in this
league. everything else you're you're
putting band-aids on on wounds left and
right trying to make up for it. Totally.
And what's wild about it is if you think
about it, like if you get four guys that
from each draft that can do that, right,
that can can fit that role and you'd say
from last year, you know, obviously
Mason Graham had a as he in his words,
he had a decent rookie season. He wants
he needs to get better, knows he needs
to get better.
>> You had the defensive rookie of the year
and Carson Swissinger. Judkins certainly
showed flashes and then Harold Fannon
was one of the most productive tight
ends in football period. So that's four
guys there. Now if one of the
quarterbacks, you know, pan out into
something, whether that even is just a
long-term backup, good. If it becomes a
long-term starter, even better, right?
Right.
>> But if you think about that, if you do
that for five straight draft classes,
that's 25. That's like half your roster
are guys in house homegrown in positions
of prominence. So that makes it so easy
then to supplement and complement that
talent with free agents.
>> Mhm.
>> And that's how you build build
championship teams. That and one of
those guys somebody in there has got to
be a quarterback. The quarterback. Yes.
That's a obviously it goes without
saying. Now you say Seattle didn't have
the quarterback. If they bring in Sam
Darnold, he plays well. They win the
Super Bowl. So there are ways to do it,
but you always have to you have to have
good quarterback play. the more guys
that you can get homegrown and you kind
of look at that Seattle team. A lot of
their top guys were drafted by them.
>> Oh, for sure.
>> Dennis Walker was drafted by them. The
offensive line was drafted. Jackson
Smith and Jig, but a lot of the
defensive studs. Now, they get Leonard
Williams. They bring him in. That
certainly helps. Um,
>> they've got, you know, their corners.
Witherspoon. A lot of those guys are all
their guys and they've done a a very
good job of then building around that,
butressing it and then going on to win
the Super Bowl. So,
there are ways to do it, but you've got
to draft effectively and well, and
somebody that in your mix, in the case
of Seattle, it was Jackson Smith and
Jigba has got to be a real
differencemaker on offense, scoring the
football.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's it's it's pretty
straightforward. You can look at the
teams that we have to contend with in
the AFC and look at how they're built
and um yeah, I mean I I think we would
all agree that that the Darnold thing is
a bit of an anomaly to take a guy who
what was he the second pick in the draft
and and went on this path and then so
the talent was there and went to
quarterback rehab. But also you have to
remember Sam Darnold could have gone a
lot of places. He looked at the
situation in Seattle and go, "Oh, I got
Jackson Smith and Jigma. I got a great
run game. I got great culture. I got a
great defense. I got a good offensive
line. Yep. I've got some stuff to work
with here. Okay, well this is an
opportunity for me to have success and
and that's the other thing. So like when
you when people talk about like doing
Darnold or something like that or even
the Stafford thing with the Rams, the
reason that that deal was able to be
done is because you could send Jared
Goff to them.
>> Yep.
>> I mean like that's there's no there's no
cheating this process.
>> No,
>> you got to draft blue chip guys.
>> Yep. Yep. So, it feels like, and I know
we'll we'll get to this with with Ben
Albbright coming up here at the top of
the hour, it does feel like the draft is
going to start at three. The more and
more you read that Arizona is up for
sale and and then it's just a matter of
what happens at one and two that would
get them the return that they want to
move back and like what's the player
that's available suddenly at three that
causes them to jump up and move back.
That's to me like that would probably be
Arvel Ree would be it. Yeah, it's
interesting though is that you know
we've heard some teams say that trading
up to three they is they're not that's
not
>> Dallas they it's too much to trade into
the top five.
>> So that tells me Dallas isn't going to a
next year one
>> right
>> that's what I would define as too much
to move up into the top five. So
everybody in the top five is saying I
need a one from next year to move out of
this. Ironically we pick at six.
>> Yep.
>> So that's
>> which and a lot of people Yeah. 12 and
20.
>> Yeah.
>> Well that's kind of why I was asking
Glenn the question earlier. It's like if
you really think that there are only so
many real firstrounders,
having three picks in the first round in
a draft that's not loaded with first
rounders doesn't make sense. Now, if the
Browns think there are 24, then they
know they're getting three of them.
That's good. So, a part of it, I think,
is just understanding exactly what is,
you know, how the Browns view it, how
the rest of the league views it is is
important, maybe less important, but you
need to understand exactly um
it's kind of like this.
>> Yeah.
>> If you're the difference between the two
and the three first rounders this year,
I think we could all agree that there
are six minimum six blue chip first
round guys in this. I'm not saying gold
jackets, but pro bowlers, there should
be six of them in this draft. And who
knows, hell, some of them could get
picked in the third, fourth round
because they're misses on this stuff all
the time.
>> But if I were to say to you, you can
have you're going to get an A for who
you take at six. You're going to get a B
minus for who you're going to take at
24, or you're going to get two B's and a
B minus. Which do you prefer?
If you're picking 12, 20, and 24, and
you're two B's and a B minus, or you get
an A and a B minus.
>> I want an A.
>> I want an A. I'm with you. I I think we
need A's.
>> Yeah.
>> So,
>> not surprisingly, you and I see that one
the same.
>> Yeah. No, I want an A.
>> I want I want an A guy, man. We need We
need foundational guys. We need some
dudes around here. It is a mailbag day
on the program. Get your questions into
us uh on the draft or anything at Browns
Daily. Also, we will take them in the
YouTube chat. You can now email your
questions to us as well at brownsradio
cleveland browns.com.
Ben Albbright put an interesting mock
draft into the ether
coming around. No big deal. No big deal.
>> Come on.
>> It's a draft.
>> God,
>> he's got it. You know, he's bringing it
for the draft.
>> Full business for the draft.
Unbelievable.
>> My my draft outfit is similar to what he
was wearing the other day.
>> Well, I was sous the sneakers. As soon
as I saw you, I was so excited because I
was just like, you look spectacular.
Like this is this is liquid gold. The
draft day Nate is ready to go. Ben
Albreight going to join us at the top of
the hour. Cleveland Browns daily. We're
presented by Valley Bet official sports
betting partner your Cleveland Browns.
Please bet responsibly and presented by
Howard Hannah official real estate
partner of your Cleveland Browns.
Second hour, Cle the Browns Daily. Time
to bet to the hotline. Our good buddy,
resident NFL insider KOA in Denver, the
great Benjamin Albbright joining us.
Buddy, uh, you fill in the blank. The
draft tonight starts at what pick for
you?
>> Oh, man. Uh, that's a good question.
First of all, fellas, Mary Dasmus.
>> Mary, buddy, we made it. Um, yeah. Yep.
Uh, you know, as far as the rest of it
goes, I mean, there was some thought
that maybe it starts at pick two with
the Ar David Bailey thing, but most
people have settled on Bailey.
Everything I've I've heard has been
settled on Bailey. Um, so I think it
really starts at pick three where you
got Arizona advertising to the entire
world that they want to go backwards.
Um, and and and what, you know,
ultimately happens with that pick. We
kind of know where four and five are are
mostly headed. And then, you know, the
next spot where everybody's got the
question mark is six. You know, we've
heard Cleveland wants to go backwards.
We've heard they love Kaden Proctor. I
don't know if that's true, but I've
heard they love him. Um, so there's, you
know, there's there's kind of three and
six are really, I think, the early pivot
points of this thing.
>> All right. You had Ben, you had a bunch
of people, friends of mine, including
the great Zash, texting me this morning
freaking out that the Browns are trading
back from 6 to 23. Like, absolutely
freaking out. You don't throw stuff out
there for no reason. So, where is this
coming from? Not necessarily from a
source standpoint, but like where you've
got an inkling about this and what would
the Browns be getting to go from six to
23?
>> Well, a lot of draft picks, potentially
a player. Um, it really that was a
combination of knowing and hearing some
things about the Browns wanting to go
backwards and then hearing things about
Philadelphia aggressively trying to go
forward. And so I just kind of married
that up and then put that together. I
realize it's a bit of a leap. Um, but
there are people freaking out here that
sort of potential there. Yeah. I I look,
I didn't mean to put anybody in a in a
tizzy. We're trying to have fun with the
mock draft. At the same time,
>> you know, Brown's Twitter, though. You
know what you you did. You You could
have picked any other team to go back 17
spots. You picked the Browns.
>> No, you know, if you think they hate me,
you should see the stuff Arizona's been
sending me for their trade back. So, um,
you know, I think, uh, and ultimately
their selection there. I think, um, you
know, I I do believe I believe they that
Cleveland wants to go backwards. they
ultimately go that far back or maybe
have a swap out with Dallas who would
like to get up and get a you know
potentially be in the Tyson situation if
he if he doesn't go five. Um you know I
I I don't know that they go that far
back but I have heard that they do want
to move back.
>> Yeah. I mean I all of those things seem
possible. Do you one thing that we've
kind of thought and with a few
exceptions potentially the Rams actually
the team that you mentioned Philly that
that most people will hold on to those
271s like grim death. Do you is does is
that what you're hearing as well that
that it's going to be very difficult to
get a 2027 one from anybody?
>> Um yeah, I think so. I think most people
recognize that next year's draft class,
you know, sort of picks back up and is
strong again. What you had was several
years of people who had COVID waiverss
and and NIL and exemptions and all that
kind of stuff. And that sort of ran out
with this draft. And so you had all
those years those layovers and and then
you had this this like this draft this
year which just doesn't have that many
top tier talent in it. and then next
year it kind of starts back over with a
bunch of top tier talent, including
quite a few quarterbacks I think people
are interested in. So, um I I think it'd
be difficult to I'm not saying
impossible, but difficult to get that.
You're not going to get the usual
premium that you get like next year. You
know, the markup is 10% on picks for
next year. You're probably not going to
get that in a trade if you do make
something like that this year.
>> Do you feel like the only teams that
would maybe even consider trading at 271
are teams like Rams, Eagles, teams that
think that their 27-1 is going to be,
you know, a bottom eight pick?
Yeah, I I think there's I think there's
truth to that. I think people that are
looking at that and saying we're in a
window or we're competitive. It's going
to be a bottom of the barrel pick in
that draft. We have we have a chance to
maybe get up and get one of these blue
chip players in this draft, you know,
and that kind of thing. I think there's
I think there's possibility for that. I
think, you know, teams like the Broncos,
teams like the um the Rams, uh you
mentioned the Eagles. Yeah, those kinds
of teams that might be willing to do
that thinking that they're going to have
lower picks in the coming draft.
>> All right. Wide receiver is a position
that we want. We want Carnell Tate at
six. A lot of Browns fans obviously want
Carnell Tate at six. Played at Ohio
State. He's been very good. Jordan
Tyson's another one. His brother plays
for the Cleveland Cavaliers. And then
Mai Lemon. Those are kind of regarded as
the three, you know, best receivers in
this draft. What have you heard on those
three and maybe likely landing spots for
them? And please say the Browns.
>> Well, I do believe the Browns will take
a receiver in the first. I'm not 100%
sure it's going to be necessarily one of
those three. Could be. Um, you know, it
just depends. Uh, there are some other
first round receivers. I mean, this is
actually a fairly decent receiver class
there at the top. You got some other
guys, Casey Conpsion, you got Boston.
You got some guys down the line at the
receiver position that uh that aren't um
that aren't that bad. So, you know, I
I'm not 100. Cooper, I didn't even
mention there is another guy. So, you
know, typically you go back and you look
at the history of Andrew Barry drafting,
he tends to draft younger guys. So, I
don't know if necessarily Cooper's his
dude, but um you know, as far as the
rest of that stuff, I think, um you
know, I think they're in play for a
receiver. The question is which one?
Tate, you know, with the Ohio State
connection makes sense. You mentioned
the Tyson connection. Um I'm just not
sure Tyson's going to be there. I I
think he's going five uh to the Giants.
We'll see if I'm if I miss on that one.
>> So, you Yeah, you you so you mentioned
Tyson and five to the Giants. You also
said you felt like four that you knew
how that one was going to go. Um how do
you think that's going to go at at four
and five? And let's say that that that
Arizona stays at three, can't do a deal,
and it's Arville Ree at three. Then what
does four and five look like in your
mind?
>> Well, then I think I think at three it
would if they stay, it might even be
Love at three. But I think some some
combination of Love, Styles, and Ree.
Um, you know, if it's not Tyson at five,
then then some combination of Love,
Styles, and Ree would be in play for
those three the three and four picks.
Uh, and then you go from there. So,
you're going to have in that situation,
let's say Love goes three. Uh, and then
let's say, you know, uh, Styles um, goes
goes four, though, that puts Ree, you
know, sliding a little bit. Uh, you may
have a team that wants to move up to
six, five or six to try to get him. But
I I would suspect in that scenario,
Tyson would go five to the Giants. And
then you're you're looking at uh, Reese
sitting there with the with the Browns
on the clock.
>> That would be an interesting scenario.
So, you feel pretty good Carell Tate
will be on the board at six when the
Browns pick. That would be an
interesting scenario because Reese would
entice some trade opportunities, but I
think it would also you might have to
sit there and say,
>> and I we want weapons, weapons, weapons,
but you might have to say maybe we want
this guy
>> to get after the quarterback with Miles
Garrett.
>> Yeah.
>> One thing I would say, I mean, look, I
know you want weapons, but the other
thing I would say is, you know, make
sure you shore up that offensive line
first. You go back and you look at what
Todd Mon did, especially as an offensive
coordinator, the system creates weapons.
If you got guys that can catch, the
system will create weapons. So maybe not
quite as big a premium. I know fans want
it, but maybe not quite as big a
premium. You want the quarterback
upright to deliver in that system.
>> Yeah, we don't want to hear that, Ben.
>> Yeah. No, no. We want a quarterback
upright and we want weapons. We want it
all. Listen, Zay Flowers goes and Zay
Flowers, Pro Bowl receiver. He helped
them out quite a bit. First round pick.
>> Yeah, there you go. There you go.
>> What do you What do you make of uh what
could happen tonight for Caleb DS?
Um, I mean, I think DS is one of the
best players in this draft. I think he
was one of the four best players. I
think he's going to go later just
because that that position that he plays
is not, you know, one of the core
premium positions. Uh, I do believe
he'll go top 15. Um, I think that, you
know, probably Baltimore is probably his
his uh, you know, floor. I don't think
he could get any later than that, but
uh, I do believe he'll probably go
somewhere in that uh, that 10 to 15
range. If he goes a few picks higher,
wouldn't surprise me, but I think that
10 to 15 range is is his money money
area. I mean, Ben is I mean, you want to
talk you So, now now I got to deal with
Kyle Hamilton and Caleb DS in Baltimore.
>> Yeah. No, thank you.
>> That's what we're doing. I mean, I
thought we're friends, right? I thought
we were friends.
>> Thank you.
>> I hope it doesn't happen. But I'm just
saying I think that's his floor. We all
know how Baltimore is. And they did that
with Hamilton. You know, guy slides in
their lap. They're going to take him.
>> Who which teams tonight do you think um
are going to be the most aggressive uh
to move up? And who are they going to be
most aggressive to move up for?
Well, I I know the Saints want to move
up. I guess that's sort of out there
because I think DJ put it out in his
mock draft, too. They've got Arville
Reese as their top player on their
board. Um, you know, I would not be
surprised if if you know, they make an
aggressive move to three to do that.
You're going to see some other players
really uh some other players trying to
trying to jockey to get up ahead of the
Lions for that offensive line run. For
some reason, people feel like that's the
sweet spot getting right in front of
Detroit. Uh, so that's the most commonly
speculated on thing is is try to get up
into the teens and make sure you get in
front of that offensive line run. that's
going to occur at some point tonight.
>> How active do you think this first
round's going to be? Like an overunder,
a Ben Albright overunder on trades just
in the first round.
>> I'm going to go with five. I I think
it's going to be pretty active. Um, you
got anytime you have a draft like this
that doesn't have a lot of top tier
talent, a lot of times you do get
movement because teams want to jockey to
make sure they get their guy. And so it
seems kind of counterintuitive that you
know in in in talent devoid drafts that
you get a lot of movement but the
reality is actually the opposite is you
know you have to make moves to go get
your guy in some of these situations. So
I expect to see you know four or five
trades tonight. I I really do.
>> Then we had a couple of teams including
the one that you talk about on a daily
basis out in Denver make make deals.
They did the waddle deal that gave up
their one and then we had the one with
Cincinnati with Dexter Lawrence uh
earlier this week. Just as a guy who's
been around the league and and knows the
minations of how things work, what do
you make of those type of moves where
you're taking kind of the bird in hand
versus the possibility of what could be.
>> Um I I think there's I think there's
value to that, especially if you believe
you're in a window. With Cincinnati, it
was kind of an eyebrow raise. They've
been shopping that pick for a while.
They offered it for Parsons and got
rebuffed. Uh I mean, it's not Parsons,
uh Max Crosby and got rebuffed. Um they
they offered uh and you know of course
to get the the Lawrence deal done.
Cincinnati nobody can figure out what
they're doing. I'm not sure they know
what they're doing but um you know end
of the day uh I think there are teams
that say okay look I can have this known
commodity now while I'm in a window
especially if I've got a a quarterback
on a rookie deal like Denver. Um or you
know I can roll the dice that the player
that I want's going to be there at 30
and you know he may or may not
contribute. You look at the Broncos last
year, their first round picks out Baron
barely played uh couldn't get on the
field because they just had, you know,
they had talent across the board in
defense. So, I I think there's something
to that, especially if you're you're
competitive in your in your win knowing
that I know what this guy is. Let's get
him in our system and let's go win some
football games.
>> Who do you think comes, let me rephrase,
is does Ty Simpson go in the first
round?
>> I believe he will. Yes.
>> Is that a is somebody trading back in to
take him?
I he could go earlier than people think.
I mean, if if he falls back there and it
gets traded into, that's fine. I I think
Arizona wants him. I think they'll move
back and I think they'll take him
earlier than people think because I
think they're worried about the Rams,
the Jets, and the Steelers all who have
put a lot of work into Ty Simpson. And
so, yeah, I think Arizona wants him. I
I'm I don't know if they take him, you
know, trade back and take him, trade
back twice and take him, um or move back
into the first, but I suspect that he
and Mendoza will both go uh in the first
round tonight. I think those are the
only quarterbacks that go in the first
round.
>> Appreciate you as always, bud. Thanks
for the time today.
>> Absolutely, guys. Take care.
>> All right, there he goes. That's Ben
Albbright, NFL insider KOA in Denver,
joining us on the hotline. We'll go
around some pre-draft questions around
the league coming up next. The mailbag
is open as and get those into Gib. You
can also do so in the YouTube chat.
You're listening to Cleveland Browns
Daily presented by Ballet Bet, official
sports betting partner, your Cleveland
Browns. Please bet responsibly.
Presented by Howard Hannah, official
real estate partner of your Cleveland
Browns.
Be sure to tune in tonight 8:00
University Hospitals Cleveland Browns
Radio Network. The Browns draft show
presented by Gregory Industry Z Ken
Carman Tyus Powell take you through the
night one of the NFL draft with
appearances from general manager Andrew
Barry and head coach Todd Monkin.
Interviews with all of our picks
tonight. Time for a pre-draft around the
league. Gibby, are you uh administering
this?
>> I can.
>> Let's do it.
>> All right. Uh, forget rankings, mocks,
everything else. Who's the best player
in this year's draft and why? You may
only pick one.
>> I'm having a Yogi Bear Dja Vu moment.
>> I could have sworn that this was with
asked. We were asked this.
>> Were we asked this yesterday or did we
just do this organically yesterday?
Tuesday.
>> We asked you to do the top five the
other day.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's top five. All
right.
>> Um,
>> I'm gonna tell you, play the tape. I'm I
my memory. I'm like an elephant.
>> So, Jeremiah Love is the best player in
this draft is what people say.
>> I I would take one of the two Buckeyes.
I'd either take downs or Styles. I got
to have one about Ree.
>> I had um I just think Ree is a Ree is
incredible, too. I I think Sunny Styles
I was talking to his position coach this
morning and um he was saying that I
said, "All right, what are you getting
with him?"
He's like, and he goes, he's Kyle Kyle
Hamilton, but more athletic and plus 25
pounds. You're getting a 12-year pro
who's going to wear a green dot who's
going to be the captain of your defense,
who's going to be the face of a
franchise. That's what you're getting.
And I said, "Okay, sold."
>> Yeah, sold. That's that feels like a
sure thing as can be. And I think
Caleb's a sure thing as well. The only
thing about Jeremiah is there's been a
lot of instances where great running
backs end up in bad spots and they can't
be productive and get hurt. And um even
last year with Ashton Genty, what was
his impact
>> in terms for the for the Raiders? Like
you hope that he gets through this and
he can get healthy and be right. Did you
get a roll with Mendoza? Right.
>> Yeah. If I had to roll on one of them, I
guess I'd roll on Styles.
>> Yeah. And what we were saying I think
when we in my mind, but we were talking
about how a lot of people actually do
have at number one on their big boards
Mendoza.
>> Yeah, that's right. That he But we
didn't think he was the best player in
this draft.
>> I don't. And do you think why do you
think people are doing that?
>> Because he's a quarterback and they know
he's going one. So it's just like it's
just easier to do
>> just say he's one and then try to slot
him in and you don't know and be
disrespectful because it doesn't matter.
He's going one. True. Yeah, it's
probably true.
>> So just it's easy. Just make him one and
then you can do everybody else. Who is
who did it end up on everybody's final
boards? Like Dane, it was Arll
is Mendoza. Was Jeremiah Mendoza?
>> I can't hear you. Gibbe,
>> I think Jeremiah was Mendoza. He was
Mendoza.
>> He was Mendoza for sure.
>> Zerine.
Um, when you go
>> I thought it was love.
>> I think Zerine's number one is either
Reese or
Bailey if I remember correctly because
you can go now to these things. Here we
go. Draft home draft tracker. Click on
that and it gives you all of his grades
prospects. His top graded prospect which
to me would be number one is Arll Reese
by quite a wide margin. By the way,
>> that was Zerine.
>> Yeah, Zerine's got him as a 7.04.
Uh, David Bailey is a 6.78. Mansour
Delane is third, Mendoza fourth,
Jeremiah Love and Mendoza are t same
grade. Carnell Tate sixth, then Bane and
then a big drop off. Maui, Noah, Styles,
DS, Lemon, Sadique, Proctor, Thano,
Jordan Tyson.
You know, um, Threes was telling me this
morning that, um, he goes, "People
think," he goes, "This is the kind of
misconception people have on Arll and
Sunny
because of our the body type of the
linebackers at Ohio State. They needed
Arll to be a pass rusher. He said, "If
we would have had a different body type
group of linebackers, I could have had
Sunny do that. He has the ability to do
that. I just didn't need him to do that
because we had Arll to do that." Um, and
he said, "Both of those guys can
actually do both things. They can both
play on off the ball and they can both
play
>> with a hand in the ground if they need
to."
>> Yep.
>> So, uh, that's type of versatility those
two cats have. PFF, by the way, on their
big board had David Bailey one,
Jeremiah Love two,
uh, actually had Ruben Bane three.
>> Ruben Bane,
>> and then Fernando Mendoza four.
>> All right. Yeah.
>> So, you got that going for you,
>> which is nice.
>> Which is very nice.
>> If Cam Ward had been in this year's
draft, would Fernando Mendoza still be
the number one quarterback on the board?
>> Who did we ask this to at the combine?
So, I'm just going to go on on the
grades of Zerline because that's the
only one I know for sure I can see.
Yeah,
>> Zerline has Cam Ward as a 6.39.
>> Mendoza was higher than that. Mendoza he
had as a 6.4
a 6.73. So, Mendoza would be number one
on his board.
>> Yeah.
>> I
>> Yeah. I mean, I I wasn't last year with
with Cam and I watched, you know, I
watch our games and I have the red zone
on, so you know, I saw quite a bit of
him. And he would do he's it wasn't
Anthony Richardson not anywhere in the
vicinity of that. But he's he's much
more accomplished, much more polished,
much better, all of that. But there is
stuff with him where like he'll make he
made a throw in the opener. I want to
say they were playing Jacksonville.
That's an alltime NFL throw.
>> Oh yeah, he made and he would do that
every week. But then there was also some
pretty stupifying stuff.
>> He got a lot final four games though he
got a lot better.
>> He did it. It it clicked for him. But
now for him now he's now new system.
>> Yep. And they need they need some
weapons for him too. Now Dable's had
some effect.
>> Lance Zerline.
I'm going to give you three guesses.
>> Okay.
>> For who Lance Zerine's NFL comp is for
Mendoza. And again 6.73. I want to go
back on the Zerline real fast and see
where that puts him in the last few
years. I have a feeling that is going to
be
>> is it all right. So comp for Mendoza,
the easy one is Cousins. Does he have
him as one of the three?
>> That is not it. No, I'm giving you three
guesses. Oh, he has Mendoza graded as
high as Caleb Williams, Jaden Daniels,
and higher than Drake May.
>> Huh.
How did he have those three rated?
>> Uh 6.74. So we would have had Caleb
01 ahead of Mendoza, Jane Daniel 6.73
and uh then Drake May 6.5
>> H. He's pretty high on him then.
>> He's quite high on him. So when you
think about from the comp standpoint,
>> I didn't see that at Indiana.
>> He was really good. I mean, he won the
Heis when they went
>> rated higher than CJ Strad.
>> We'll see. I mean, who knows? His play
is pro comp for Mendoza is Joe Burrow.
>> Oh, that I don't know about that. We'll
see.
>> I'm just saying that's what he said.
Now, his grade for Joe Burrow was
significantly higher, but the way that
he plays the game is what he's saying.
>> So, I think what you have to do, I
always do this and I I didn't even know
this. I'm just pulling it up. Let's just
see how he did in the in the best
biggest games they played. Um against
Oregon, he was 20. This was all the way
back in October. Uh he was and they won
every game they played, just to
remember. uh 20 of 31, 215, one
touchdown, one pick. So 64% completions
against Ohio State in the Big 10
Championship. 15 to 23, 222 a touchdown
and a pick. That was against the number
one defense in the country. Against
Bama, he was elite. 14- 16, 192, three
touchdowns, no picks. Crazy good against
Oregon the second time. 17 to 20, 177,
five touchdowns, no picks. Um not a lot
down the field with him. And then in
this national championship game, 16 to
27, 186, no touchdowns, no picks. In
fact, boy, I don't know if this has ever
happened. When do you think's the last
time a quarterback number went number
one overall and did not throw for 300
yards in a single game of his last
season in college football?
>> It's a good question.
>> Not once. He didn't throw for 300 once.
He threw for 299 against Wisconsin.
That's it. And honestly,
the next Oh, no. No, I take that. I
Sorry, I missed one. He threw for 332
against uh Michigan State. My bad.
>> All right, good.
>> 332.
>> Not even a Penn State comeback.
>> No, Penn State was 218.
>> Oh, that's right. They were awful till
the final eight minutes of the game.
>> Yeah, he lit up Michigan State 24 to 28,
332, four touchdowns, no picks, so he
had he had the one.
>> Maybe that new coach will be better at
Penn State. Doubtful, though.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You rarely see it.
Uh, if Cardell Tate is the best wide
receiver in this draft, who's number two
and why?
>> Good question.
And I think that there might be two
reasonable answers. Um,
there are I think if you want an in
inside guy, it's Mai Lemon. And some
people would argue that Mai Lemon is
>> absolutely the second best receiver in
this draft. If you want an outside guy
who's twitchy and explosive and big and
can jump and do all of those things,
then it's it's Jordan Tyson who's evokes
being a more athletic Stefon Diggs. Um,
that's from Dane Bugler. So, that to me
is it's just kind of more what your
flavor is.
>> It's totally in the eye of the beholder
with those two guys. And maybe Tyson's
ahead of Tate on some people's. The big
thing everyone was waiting for was the
medicals on him. Uh, in terms of once
you get past that, I really like Omar
Cooper and I like Denzel Boston. I like
both those guys.
>> I like Denzel Boston as well. I'm with
you. And Omar Cooper,
>> I am a big Denzel Boston fan.
>> He's made a lot of plays. Um,
but yeah, I I like him. I like him.
>> Speaking of the Buckeyes, ranked the top
four Buckeyes in this draft from first
to fourth.
Caleb, Sunny, Arll, Carnell.
>> Yeah. Um,
>> like that.
>> I'm
>> I think they're all going to be just
fine.
>> I'm going to go one of them, but I I'd
go that way. I guess
>> Reese Downs, Carnell, Sunny.
>> Not that there's anything against I just
I also want I just don't want Carnell to
be last.
This is one of those ones where he's
like the valadictorian in a you know
he's magnum but there's sumakum lada.
Yeah. They're all great. There's not
going to be this isn't validictorian to
summer school. They're all going to be
really really good.
>> Uh little overunder fun. How many trades
happened in night one? Overund's five
and a half.
>> Under.
>> Well, it sure sounded like under, right?
It sounded like we've heard a lot of
people say five is the number. So that's
going to be under. I over is more fun.
I'll say over. Why not? I mean
>> it's more enjoyable. Yeah,
>> that'd be fun. We have a tradeing
ding ding.
>> That'd be great.
>> It's fun when you get those. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Absolutely.
>> Well, when was last year?
>> Usually now such and such is on the
clock.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. When last year did we
did Did the the trade that we did with
Jacksonville? When was that consumate?
Wasn't that right before 7 o'clock?
>> No, it was on Was it six o'clock? When
did When did that What time did that
deal come down?
>> On the clock. Well,
>> no, no, but it was reported.
>> We we had we had some inkling like at
7:55 that something might be coming
down. It was literally right before,
>> but it was not because had the Titans
not taken Cam Ward,
>> the trade was off,
>> right? So, you need
>> So, you needed that to happen. But, was
it not not reported before the draft
started?
>> It wasn't. So, okay. I was trying to
remember how that all worked. I guess in
my head I thought it was
>> it was reported before that.
>> No, we had an inkling that there could
be a trade. Yes,
>> but not
>> what or any anything like that.
>> Final one. Low over under. Ty Simpson's
draft pick number 24 and a half. Over,
under,
>> over,
>> out of the first round.
>> So, he goes first back end.
>> So, there are a lot of people that are
saying, which would lend your to the
underside of this, that Arizona is going
to trade back from three to eight.
>> That'd be the Saints
>> with the Saints.
>> Yep. And then they're going to take him
there at eight. If you believe in him,
you believe in it. To me, it's like if
you believe him, if he's a quarterback,
you believe him.
>> Great point on you. And sometimes we do
that. Like we say, well, why would you
take him at eight? Well, if you think
he's a franchise quarterback, he's worth
it. What do you care? Yeah. Um sometimes
I think sometimes I think we do what I
do. I think NFL teams do what I just did
right there, which is you get greedy and
you're like, "Well, I'm not going to
take him at eight. I can get him at 26
and I'm going to get this guy at 8 and
then I'm going to wait and I'll get him
at 26." But then maybe you miss. If you
have conviction, just take your guy.
>> And here's the reality of the situation.
Whether he's a miss at eight or he's a
miss at 26 doesn't matter. He's a miss.
And if he's a hit, it also doesn't
matter.
>> No.
>> No, it doesn't.
>> I just have one other question for Bo
Bishop. Your thought when you saw that
Alabama extended Kalin Dour $12.5
million a year.
>> What about college football? Nate gets
no say in this.
>> Well, we'll get to you. College football
Nate.
>> Do you want to weigh in first? I'll see
the floor.
>> Yeah, I think it's I I got to tell you
something, it's a little rich for my
blood.
>> This is a program that is rudderless
right now without Nick Sabin and
>> without any money.
>> Without any money.
>> Well, what are they giving it to him
for? This is This is not a great No,
>> that is that is not going over well in
this room.
>> Which part?
>> They're the cousin of the cousin of
Pedman is here.
>> What's his thoughts?
>> Does he like it?
>> He He thinks you're an idiot.
Alabama is not rudderless.
>> They are rudderless.
>> They just made the playoff.
>> Whatever. Here's a boring.
>> They're probably going to have a
quarterback take it in the first round.
>> Did they just get bounced?
>> Second. Hold on just a second.
>> When did they get bounced, young
Gabriel?
>> To the best team in the the nation.
>> Do you know why this happened? Do you
know why you want the real truth on why
this happened?
>> You an idiot.
>> Do you want You want the real truth on
why this happened?
>> Okay.
>> This happened because of Chiron Moore.
And this deal was written all the way
back then and it took this long to have
it go public. He was he was in at
Michigan and he leveraged the Michigan
situation.
>> Yep.
>> To get the extension at Alabama. That's
why that happened.
>> We'll open up the mailbag coming up
next. Cleveland Browns daily 8:50 ESPN.
Car, truck, or motorcycle accident cause
you injury? Call the injury lawyers at
1800 Elk Ohio for a free case review.
Elken Elk, proud partner of your
Cleveland Browns. Time to open up that
mailbag on a draft day Thursday edition.
Get your questions into the fellas at
Browns Daily on the X or hit us up in
the YouTube chat. We can answer those
live as well. Hello, Gibbe.
>> Hi.
>> How are you? Trey Kerry wants to know,
"Would you trust young Gabriel or Dr.
Jay to run the team for the next 10
years?"
>> Young Gabriel,
>> no disrespect to Dr. J.
>> No, I think Dr. Jay,
>> it's a tough question.
>> Dr. J's happy to be
>> Here's the thing about Young Gabriel. If
it all goes to hell, he can do standup
comedy.
>> He can do Yeah. So, the pressers, you
did have Glenn Roland in here.
>> I'm selfish. I'm I just like give me
content. What's fun? Like, so I think
now Well, hold on.
>> Dr. Jay's pressor.
>> I just don't know if Dr. Jay's could be
allowed on the FCC.
>> That's true.
>> Whereas I like Young Gabriel, I think
you're getting a lot of you get a lot of
voice material.
>> Young Gabriel is going to run.
>> Young Gabriel should be on Saturday
Night Live.
>> Dr. Jay is going to be a part of the uh
of the marketing and branding though and
the fashion, the the fits.
>> No, there's no question. Yeah, there's
no question.
>> We're in good hands here.
>> And he'll also be involved in the
weather and updating people at night. No
sun.
>> That's right.
In four hours, there will be no sun.
>> No sun.
>> We'll be drafting. There will be no sun.
>> There will be no sun.
>> Uh Gman's burner account says, "Happy
draft day, boys from the burner network.
>> Surprised Gibby not in his second home
in Pukesburg."
>> Fair.
>> One of the all-time great bits was how
much you loved when we were had the when
you had your second home,
>> the undisclosed location.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> You loved it so much.
>> I miss it.
Who wouldn't?
>> A couple weeks ago, we had Isaiah
Magguire in here. I go, "Do you remember
the first time I interviewed you?" He
goes,
>> "Yeah, it was at some place you called
the undisclosed location." I was like,
"Yeah, right through the fence."
>> Yeah, right there.
>> The undisclosed location.
>> Stfansky came in there once. Remember he
drove his SUV over
>> like it was a who's who.
>> Really was.
>> I had a grill. I had a fresh beer.
>> Living your best life. Well, that's what
it'll be like in the new digs.
>> Oh, man.
>> Whatever we want.
>> I'm actually That's a pretty good idea.
If I could just bring the grill out into
the middle of the practice field.
>> Now we're talking.
>> Yep. That's it.
>> Hey, we have a uh a statement from the
Patriots
>> on uh the uh Mike Vrabel situation. The
New England Patriots fully support Mike
Vrabel's decision to prioritize his
family first as well as his own
well-being. Mike has been open with us
about his commitment to being the best
version of himself for his family, his
team, and his our and our fans, and we
expect the steps he is taking to follow
through on that commitment. We are
confident in the leadership and
communication Mike has established with
our personnel personnel staff throughout
this pre-draft process. While he will
not be present at the facility on
Saturday, we know that the draft
evaluations are complete, and Elliot
Wolf and his personnel staff are
prepared to execute our draft as planned
this weekend. There you go.
>> All right, there it is.
Um, the burner, by the way, asked, "What
are your all-time draft great and
jaw-dropping moments?"
I will say and I know that it didn't
work out but in terms of the fun of it
when the Browns I was in Radio City
Musical and the Browns came back on the
clock at picked 22 in the 2014 draft and
picked John football the buzz
>> cuz everybody knew that's what it had to
be. They came back in, they picked
Johnny football and it was just pure
electricity. And I remember being
walking home to my hotel from that. So
much energy. We were like the talk of
the town and uh Luminary at the time
drives by in their big, you know, SUV or
whatever that they were being driven
around, rolls the windows down, starts
screaming all kinds of hilarious and
crazy things about the greatness that
was going to ensue for all of us from
that was certainly one of my great draft
moments. I
>> I missed the draft there.
>> I I I've been there for many drafts and
it's it was awesome. Um, that was
actually my first draft covering for the
Browns and I actually I nailed that we
were going to trade down, take a corner
and then trade back up and take
quarterback and I knew
nothing about what the actual plans
were. Yeah, that year. But it's funny
Jeff McN once made a video. I'd say
something and be like check and it ended
up working out. Um cuz if you would
asked me what I thought was going to
happen prior to that based on my
knowledge, I would have thought a
different quarterback was going to be
drafted right there at right at the top
right where it was. And then I found out
that we were not taking anybody there,
which was also surprising. A lot of
talent in that draft.
>> Pretty good draft.
>> An unreal draft if you actually look
back at it. 2014 is an unreal draft.
>> Yeah, it's not it's not a lot of fun.
>> Unfortunately, two first round picks who
did not
>> stay in the NFL in the entirety of their
rookie contracts.
>> Mine was 07. I had just moved here from
Florida and uh my wife's family has had
had brown sticks forever and I mean one
of the first things I did when I met her
family
>> um was we went we went to dinner
Saturday night uh and then at Corleó and
then um of course and then Sunday we did
chop house brunch and we went down his
birthday went down to do the uh went
down to the Browns game and so
>> in in ' 07 and you already had you had
you had Kellen Winsow Jr. you just
acquired Jamal Lewis, you had Brillian
Edwards. Like, you had some pieces and
it was just like, oh man, if you just
get the quarterback and then you get a
guy named Joe Thomas in the first. Okay,
sure thing. Way we go on that. Nobody
knew he was going to be what he became,
but certainly pretty good. And then
Brady Quinn and you think, my god, Brady
Quinn fell. I mean, that's a Dublin
Kaufman kid and I was down in Columbus
at the time and it's like, holy hell,
they just landed their left tackle and
their quarterback in one draft. Is that
one of the first times that you and I
ever worked together?
>> That's right.
>> Was it?
>> Yeah,
>> that's right. We were I could talk about
the place now because it's closed and
God rest his soul Eddie Alman who owned
Harpos Gage Shopping Center.
>> Yeah.
>> We always did draft there.
>> Mhm.
>> Uh with ESPN.
>> Um and at that time the draft started at
noon on Saturday.
>> It did. Y
>> and the first three rounds were on
Saturday and everything else was on
Sunday. I mean but it went to like 10:00
at night on Saturday
>> and we take Joe Thomas. Now, at the
time, Eddie, bit of a penny pincher, but
clearly a smart businessman. He didn't
give away his product for free.
>> Yep.
>> He wouldn't he would he was like, "I'm
not comping any food. I'm not comping
any beverages. Nothing." I'm like, "We
are at your location for 12 hours."
>> Like, come on. What What What are we
doing here? And he goes, "No, you got to
pay for everything." I said, "The hell I
am."
So, I literally pulled up an ESPN
Cleveland van
>> van. You had a
>> unmarked
>> and I set up a free buffet for my talent
in the van.
>> Yeah, he had a food van. I remember
that.
>> That's incredible.
>> Give a legend.
>> So, I'm in the van eating spaghetti.
We're having pasta and we're listening
to the show while we're in this van
right out front
>> and all of a sudden they're like, "The
helmet's changed.
And I almost knocked myself out standing
up in the van trying to get out to get
back in and the place lost its mind. The
only time it's been that crazy was
Johnny Manzel as well.
>> Yeah, it had to be. I mean, because
everybody knew Brady. He's an Ohioan.
He's a coffin kid and then he was a
four-year starter at Notre Dame. Like it
was
>> and he had a good really good senior
year. here. I mean, they they did they
No, they lost USC on the tush push with
Bush and Liner, but but he was and yeah,
and that's goes that's one I obviously
know Brady well now and um one of those
situations where different spot like
things just didn't align. You know,
there's so many factors that make
quarterback tough.
>> Uh love a dog today. I've heard Tate
compared to Amari Cooper and Tyson
compared to OBJ this week. If you had
the choice between OBJ or Amari, who
would you choose and why?
>> I mean, you're just hoping that they
stay healthy, but Pico OBJ was better
than Picamari. I mean, higher ceiling
for sure. Now, he flamed out due to
injuries and Amari is a constant
professional and a great player. I don't
think you go wrong with either one, but
like if you're looking for a needle
mover, I mean, what Odell Beckham Jr.
did his first four years in the league
was astonishing. It was I think your
your your the answer to your if that is
what you believe it to be love a dog
today what I would say is that your
answer is in the eye of the beholder
would you rather have somebody who had a
12 10 year 11 year NFL career was a pro
bowler multiple times in various parts
of his NFL career or a comet who burned
out because of injury and wasn't able to
stay on the field. So, not to say that
those two guys are that, but I if if
you're saying philosophically this guy's
this, this guy's that, that's what
you're asking. I I would rather have
Cooper cuz I'd rather have a guy who's
here for 10 years, makes six Pro Bowls,
and is a dude I can rely upon for a
bunch of times to put on the side of the
building.
Dog Pound Cleveland Brown says, "Where
can I watch listen to Nate and Ken's
draft show tonight?" Also, is Gerro
going to be with you guys again? Tonight
it will be Ken, Nathan, and Tyus Powell
at 8:00 p.m.
>> Gerrod will be on tomorrow night with
Siciliano. Uh, and Ken and Nathan, um,
you unfortunately can't watch us. The
NFL doesn't allow for live streaming.
>> Really?
>> They want your eyeballs on their stuff.
>> Oh, really?
>> So, we're not allowed to stream
>> uh in the last couple of years postco.
>> Oh, okay. So, yeah, because there was
one year, remember we live streamed Joe
Thomas eating 14 plates of food and five
plates of desserts.
>> That's right.
>> Yellowstone, by the way, has a question
about food. Did you see this?
>> Yeah.
>> Um,
uh, Yellowstone, shout out. I think he's
in the STL now. Can we get an early
scouting report on the dinner situation
tonight?
>> I don't know. There's a series on HBO
about the STL that just finished.
>> That's right. That's right. sad. I ended
up being sad. It's very sad.
>> It's a It's a mission barbecue night for
dinner. And then the late night snack,
which is the same size as the dinner, is
a Hawaiian theme. There's some jerk
chicken wings that are right on the uh
>> on the menu that are standing out.
There's a number of things I'm
interested in.
>> I think Did I see uh some dumplings?
>> I think so. Tomorrow night's the big
one. Tomorrow night's the the grandiose.
I believe we got steak and sea bass and
wins.
>> Nice. Who used to do this?
>> Yeah.
>> Who was that?
>> Simone tech.
>> Oh my god. Simone with his stakes that
we had to pay for.
>> We had to pay for it. Yep. That's right.
>> That was his move when he thought we
were going to be paying for him.
>> Oh yeah. Yeah.
>> And then turns out we did pay for him.
>> Yeah, we did pay as it turns out. And he
used Poliola.
>> Uh, a couple questions from the YouTube.
Stony Juan, why do we hear everyone
else's name besides uh Lomu for a
projected left tackle pick? We hear
Fano's name. He wasn't even the left
tackle for Utah.
>> Well, if we take Thano, I don't think we
he would be playing left tackle. I think
he'd be playing right tackle.
>> Yeah, Lomu certainly could be in the mix
at 24.
>> I mean, it seems like that the left
tackles are
the uh Proctor
and the kid from Georgia.
>> Mhm.
>> And they're both they both Monroe
Freeling, but they just are a little
raw.
>> Yep. Um Blake Miller could be a a left
tackle, right tackle.
>> Good Strongsville kid. Yeah.
>> Uh Patriot Brand asks, "Where did Bo get
his quarter zip? It's fantastic."
>> Well, thank you. Um
I think it's I think it's Peter Malar.
>> Well, there you go.
>> Seems appropriate.
>> Uh Tommy Clo, if you didn't have to be
on air tonight, what would the ideal NFL
draft night viewing entail?
I don't have to be on air tonight. So,
what it'll the boys will get done with
uh lacrosse practice around 7 something
like that. And so, when we'll have the
spread out and we'll be ready to go.
It's a beautiful night. I might get
crazy and do it outside.
>> Pool's open.
>> 77 78°.
>> Nobody's going to get hurt. I think I'm
going to do it outside. Get bring the
TVs outside and live a little bit
>> if you need to. You go jacuzzi. Pacuzzi.
If it's a little too cold, gets a little
too cold. Be a guy to go jacuzzi.
Yeah, very what a setup. So I I still I
can't wait to see it when I bring
transform tweets at the show.
>> Can you guys tell me who the Browns pick
Saturday? Pretty sure they recorded that
last night and I'm pretty sure you guys
were there.
>> That's a good That's
>> That's old, man. That's That's a great
job.
>> That's deep.
>> Good tweeting.
>> That's a great job. That's good
tweeting.
>> That is very good.
That is that's good effort. Good effort
there.
>> Yeah. Uh,
apprentice premiere. What pick tonight
will drive you absolutely crazy and
disappointment? Uh,
>> I don't want to do that for fear that
this audio lives.
>> Let's go this Let's go this route. Let's
go. You got a bold prediction for
tonight's NFL draft. Period. Not for us.
Bold prediction for the draft.
>> There's been instances on this program
where you and I have said things about
people who were damn near hired here.
>> Yep.
>> Damn near ended up here. So I I What
were you So then take us out of it. Does
that
>> We had one who almost
>> played here.
>> That's right.
>> But then didn't
>> but didn't close.
>> Close.
>> Boy, I'm surprised that audio was never
dug up.
>> Cuz why would it be?
>> Thank god we have good people who didn't
>> because people that's part of the job
too. Like part of the job is liking
certain things and then not liking other
things just because they exist. Gibbe is
the one who violates that his love for
>> probably the lowhanging fruit on your to
answer your question is it will drive me
nuts if Caleb DS falls to the Ravens at
whatever
>> like that would drive me nuts that would
physically make me ill like
>> yeah Ben Albbright said that he's like
you know like the floor on Caleb is
Baltimore at 15 or wherever they pick
and I'm like I'm like no I that would
that would make me violently ill like I
don't I don't need Caleb DS playing for
Baltimore with Kyle Hamilton. I don't
need that.
>> Nope. Mm-m.
I don't know if I've got any. Oh, here
we go. Now they're coming in.
>> Two minutes. Two minutes.
>> Coming in a few more.
>> Draft your perfect fast food meal. Mix
entree, fries, drinks, desserts from any
franchise.
>> I think my perfect fast food I'd
probably have a spicy chicken sandwich
from Chick-fil-A. I'd have a couple of
chicken soft tacos fresca style from
Taco Bell. Well, I'd probably do a
fajita burrito and then one as my
indulgence back when they had those like
volcano tacos when they had that like
the red shell that was spicy and Yeah.
One of those.
>> Yeah. There we go.
>> I think my favorite I Chick-fil-A is
kind of borderline I know it is, but
it's kind of almost It is, but it's
almost
>> I love their breakfast. I'm not as keen
on
>> You don't like the sandwiches?
Sandwiches?
>> Not really. That sandwich is nice.
>> Sandwiches kind of undefeated, I think.
Um I my my
>> There we go. Bring in the treats. Let's
go.
>> A friend of ours just tweeted out put on
Facebook a video of her son as like a
four. That's a great lavel our who just
walked by. Uh her son like they he was
used to be at our club and they did an
Easter egg hunt and they put out the
Easter eggs and her son who I coach with
my with Bootsie. Her son went sprinting
out to get an Easter egg and took out
his legs and Lavell somehow kept his
bearings and didn't go all the way to
the ground and got up on his own.
Athlete.
>> Athlete.
>> I'll show it to you. I'll show it to
you. It's pretty good.
>> He's lucky he didn't turn AC.
>> Very good. Um well, here we I guess
tomorrow we'll be doing it. We'll know.
>> We'll know something.
>> Dane Bugler will join us tomorrow. Our
draft pick.
>> You guys both at the same time go we'll
know something.
>> We will. We're going to put something
tomorrow. Can't you can't say we won't.
No.
>> Have a good night tonight, boys. Knock
it out of the park as I know that you
will. Thanks for listening, everybody.
Cleveland Runs Daily presented by Valley
Bet, official sports betting partner of
your Cleveland Browns. And please bet
responsibly and presented by Howard
Hannah, official real estate partner of
your Cleveland Browns on 850 ESPN
Cleveland.